<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Peter Yin</title>
    <link>http://peteryin.fyi/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Peter Yin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 13:06:05 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://peteryin.fyi/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>TLDR: The Precision of Sensory Evidence</title>
      <link>http://peteryin.fyi/tldr-the-precision-of-sensory-evidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 13:06:05 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://peteryin.fyi/tldr-the-precision-of-sensory-evidence/</guid>
      <description>In The Precision of Sensory Evidence, Scott Alexander discusses a new theory behind depression and other negative emotions. As someone who is higher in neuroticism, I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a lot of time thinking of ways to improve my mental wellbeing, but not as much on what might cause my predisposition to negative emotions in the first place.
It&amp;rsquo;s a thought-provoking read, but it&amp;rsquo;s also a bit difficult to parse. This is my attempt to distill the main ideas and my personal takeaways so I can revisit them in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Imagining a Better Social Media</title>
      <link>http://peteryin.fyi/imagining-a-better-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 09:54:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://peteryin.fyi/imagining-a-better-social-media/</guid>
      <description>Social media has seen better days Between the negative impacts on mental health, the spread of disinformation, and concerns with data privacy, the problems with social media seem more in the spotlight than ever before. The Social Dilemma, a recent Netflix documentary highlighting these problems (with help from the people who created them), has reached 100 million people in 190 countries 1. It’s no exaggeration to say the problems with social media are a mainstream topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nobody Told Me</title>
      <link>http://peteryin.fyi/nobody-told-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 11:35:46 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://peteryin.fyi/nobody-told-me/</guid>
      <description>Nobody told me that it&amp;rsquo;s ok to pause
To sit and wait for a worthy cause
That you can be moving through the world or the world can be moving towards you
That if you take the first step then the universe will take 100 steps towards you
That if you write the first sentence, the next sentences will write themselves
This is the art of letting go
Of surrendering to the universal flow</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
